Finding Aid for Medical School (University of Michigan) records, 1850-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Subordinate Administrative Officers 1929-1998
  - Associate Dean Giles Bole 1986-1991
    - Medical Service Plan (MSP)
      - Budgets 1987-1990 (Box 254)
      - Category II Risk 1988-1990 (Box 255)
      - Director Search 1987 (Box 255)
      - Executive Committee 1986-1989 (Box 255)
      - General 1986-1989 (Box 255)
      - Governance 1986-1989 (Box 255)
      - Medicare 1990 (Box 255)
      - Reimbursement 1988-1990 (Box 255)
    - M-CARE (Health Maintenance Organization)
      - Advertising 1988-1990 (Box 255)
      - Articles and Bylaws 1986-1988, 3 folders (Box 255)
      - Audit 1987 (Box 255)
      - Benefits 1990 (Box 255)
      - Billi, Dr. John E. 1987-1989 (Box 255)
      - Board of Directors 1988-1990 (Box 255)
      - Boles/Forsyth/Porwal Conference 1988 (Box 255)
      - Business Plan 1988 (Box 255)
      - Certification 1987-1988 (Box 255)
      - Charges 1988 (Box 255)
      - Contracts 1987-1991 (Box 255)
      - Credentialing 1986-1988 (Box 255)
      - Emergency Services 1989-1990 (Box 255)
      - Enrollments 1987-1990 (Box 255)
      - Family Practice 1986-1990 (Box 255)
      - Finances 1987-1990 (Box 255)
      - Future Options 1988-1991 (Box 255)
      - General 1986-1991, 3 folders (Box 255)
      - HMO (Health Maintenance Organization) 1986-1991 (Box 256)
      - HMO Background Articles 1986-1991 (Box 256)
      - House Officer Orientation 1988 (Box 256)
      - Internal Medicine 1986-1987 (Box 256)
      - IPA (Independent Practice Association) 1987-1991, 2 folders (Box 256)
      - Legal 1988-1990 (Box 256)
      - Major Medical 1987-1990 (Box 256)
      - Managed Care Task Force 1990 (Box 256)
      - Medical Director Position 1988 (Box 256)
      - Member Handbook (HMO, Major Medical) 1987 (Box 256)
      - Michigan Health Care Network 1988 (Box 256)
      - Obstetrics and Gynecology 1986-1989 (Box 256)
      - Peat Marwick Consultants 1988 (Box 256)
      - Pediatrics 1988-1989 (Box 256)
      - Phase I Data 1988 (Box 256)
      - Physician Providers 1987-1990 (Box 256)
      - Podiatry 1989 (Box 256)
      - Policies and Procedures 1988 (Box 256)
      - Porwal, Mike 1988-1989 (Box 256)
      - Prescription Drugs 1988 (Box 256)
      - Preferred Provider Organization Task Force Report 1984 (Box 256)
      - President 1987-1990 (Box 256)
      - Provider Directories 1987-1988 (Box 256)
      - Psychiatry 1987-1990 (Box 256)
      - Primary Care 1986-1990 (Box 256)
      - Rates 1988-1991 (Box 256)
      - Reimbursement Methodology 1987 (Box 256)
      - Reorganization 1987-1988 (Box 256)
      - Sale or Merger 1989 (Box 256)
      - Satellites 1986-1989 (Box 256)
      - Settlement 1988-1990, 2 folders (Box 256)
      - Space 1988 (Box 256)
      - Staff Model 1986-1988 (Box 256)
      - Teamsters Negotiations 1988 (Box 256)
      - UMMC (University of Michigan Medical Center) Agreement 1989 (Box 256)
      - University Departments 1987-1988 (Box 256)
      - University Health Service 1988-1989 (Box 256)
      - Utilization 1988-1990 (Box 256)
      - Work Group 1987-1988 (Box 256)
    - Miscellaneous 1986-1990 (Box 257)
    - Personnel-Paid Time Off Study 1988 (Box 257)
    - Provost for Medical Affairs 1977-1978 (Box 257)
    - Research
      - General 1986-1989, 4 folders (Box 257)
      - Core Facilities 1989 (Box 257)
      - Intellectual Properties 1989 (Box 257)
      - Space Allocation Policy task Force 1988 (Box 257)
    - Resident County Health Program 1986 (Box 257)
    - Retirement Furloughs 1989 (Box 257)
    - Transplant and Health Policy Center 1985-1990 (Box 257)
    - Veterans Administration Hospital 1984-1989, 6 folders (Box 257)
  - Associate Dean for Clinical Affairs John E. Billi 1990-1998
    The files of John E. Billi, Associate Dean for Clinical Affairs (6 linear feet, 1990-2002) focus on managed care issues, including efforts to establish a management services organization, provider networks, Medicare, as well as more general clinical management issues. Also are included are talks and presentations by Billi on a variety of topics.
    - Outgoing Correspondence 1990-1992, 18 folders (Box 258)
    - Outgoing Correspondence 1993-April 1998, 11 folders (Box 259)
    - Management (Provider) Services Organization--MP(S)O
      - MSO AHEC [Area Health Education Center] Grant 1995-1996 (Box 318)
      - MPSO Presentation
        - Budget 1995-1996 (Box 318)
        - Development Team 1995-1996 (Box 318)
      - MSO RFP for Business Plan 1995 (Box 318)
      - Bound Reports and Loose Papers: MSO RFP Evaluations 1995 (Box 318)
      - MPSO Presentation: 10 Context Areas Folders
        - 10 Context Areas--Education 1996 (Box 318)
        - 10 Context Areas--Info System 1995-1996 (Box 318)
        - 10 Context Areas--Legal/Corporate 1995 (Box 318)
        - 10 Context Areas--Managed Care Business Ops 1995 (Box 318)
        - 10 Context Areas--Medical Management 1995-1996 (Box 318)
        - 10 Context Areas--Network Development 1995-1996 (Box 318)
        - 10 Context Areas--Office Management 1995 (Box 318)
      - MSO--Pilots/General 1995 (Box 318)
      - MPSO Presentation
        - Progress Reports 1995 (Box 318)
        - Literature/Reports 1994-1995 (Box 318)
      - MSO Presentation Materials 1994-1995 (Box 318)
      - MSO Present 1993-1995 (Box 318)
      - Old MSO 1995 (Box 318)
      - MSO Presentations 1995 (Box 318)
      - MSO Presentation Drafts 1995 (Box 318)
      - MSO Decision 1995-1996 (Box 318)
      - MPSO Presentation
        - Consultant Info 1995-1996 (Box 318)
        - Regions/POs [Physicians' Organizations] 1995-1996 (Box 318)
      - MSO PO-Jackson 1995 (Box 318)
      - MSO-Kalamazoo "Physicians for Patients" Group 1995-1996 (Box 318)
      - Dr. Gary D. Maynard (Box 318)
      - MSO-Lakeside 1995 (Box 318)
      - MSO-Livingston 1995 (Box 318)
      - MSO-Mayo 1996 (Box 318)
      - MSO-MPRO (MI Peer Review Organization) 1996 (Box 318)
      - MSO-Mid-Michigan 1995-1996 (Box 318)
      - MPSO Presentation--Regions/POs--NPO [Northern MI Physicians' Organization] 1995 (Box 318)
      - Oakwood MSO 1996 (Box 318)
      - MSO-MSMS (MI State Medical Society) 1995-1997 (Box 318)
      - MSO To Do 1995 (Box 318)
      - UM Physician Organizations 1994-1995 (Box 318)
      - UM Out State Physician Model 1993-1995 (Box 319)
      - MSO EYENET 1995 (Box 319)
      - I.R.2 PHYCOR 1995 (Box 319)
      - MSO: PhyCor (Box 319)
      - Additional PhyCor Materials 1995 (Box 319)
      - MPO 1998 (Box 319)
      - Med School & Hospital strategic plans 1993-1995 (Box 319)
      - Miscellaneous Strategic Planning and MI Health Corporation Papers 1993, 2000 (Box 319)
      - UM Hospital & Health Center Ambulatory Care Strategy Development (Binder) 1998 (Box 319)
      - FGP (Faculty Group Practice) 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box 319)
      - UMMSIP 1994 (Box 319)
      - IPA Management 1994-1995 (Box 319)
      - Clinical Affairs Reorganization 1994 (Box 319)
      - Financial Redesign 1994-1995 (Box 319)
      - Henry Ford and HAP 1996-1999 (Box 319)
      - MI Provider Network (papers and bound reports) 1994-1996 (Box 319)
      - MI Provider Network 1993-1996, 2 hanging file folders (Box 320)
    - Health Services Research Initiative 1998-2000 (Box 320)
    - Miscellaneous Papers 2000-2001 (Box 320)
    - Medicaid Rebid 2000-2001 (Box 320)
    - Medicare, BCBS [Blue Cross/Blue Shield], and Teaching Physician Billing Regulations
      - Neurology [Medicare] Audit: Upcoding 1993 (Box 320)
      - Teaching Physician Task Force (I.D.2.A) 1996 (Box 320)
      - Teaching Physician HO Supervision / IL 372 (I.D.A) 1992-1995 (Box 320)
      - Medicare-Teaching / Attending 1993-1996 (Box 321)
      - AAMC-Medicare Teaching Regulations (Box 321)
      - BCBS 90 (I.D.1.e.-Blue Chip Audit) 1990-1991 (Box 321)
      - Teaching Physician Task Force/BCBS/Medicare Billing papers 1996 (Box 321)
      - Medicare PC Exception 1996 (Box 321)
      - Documentation E + M (I.D.2.h) 1992-1995 (Box 321)
      - I.D.3.-Medicaid 1993-1995 (Box 321)
      - BCBS-Phys (I.D.1.d.) 1994-1995 (Box 321)
      - Dept. Compliance and Attendance 1996 (Box 321)
    - Utilization
      - M-CARE Utilization Reports 1990-1991 (Box 321)
      - 1992 M-CARE Utilization, 1993 (Box 321)
      - M-CARE Utilization 1992-1993 (Box 321)
      - M-CARE Utilization 1991-1993 (Box 321)
      - UM-IPA Utilization-1991--also titled "MSPEC [Medical Service Plan Executive Committee] Utilization Report, 11-24-92" (Box 321)
      - MSPEC M-CARE Utilization Report (Box 321)
      - MSPEC 2-23-1993 (Box 321)
      - MSPEC UR Charge Backs 1991 (Box 321)
    - Talks
      - Critical Evaluations of Drug Trials 1985 (Box 322)
      - Cost 1987 (Box 322)
      - Cost Talk 1982-1987 (Box 322)
      - I.M.1-Ethics of Capitation 1986 (Box 322)
      - I.M.2-Update on HMO & PPO 1990 (Box 322)
      - Readmission Talk 1991 (Box 322)
      - Council of Deans-Gikas 1996 (Box 322)
      - Council of Deans-Gikas 1993-1995 (Box 322)
      - "Managed Care [and the] AMC [Academic Medical Center]" (Box 322)
      - SGIM 4/93--Managed Care/AMC 1993 (Box 322)
      - Chamber of Commerce 1996 (Box 322)
      - Talks-Exit Interview 1996-1997 (Box 322)
      - Practice Guidelines (Box 322)
      - "Faculty Education Managed Care"
        - Department Meetings re: M-Care 1992 (Box 322)
    - Clinical and Practice Management
      - 1993-1996, 13 folders (Box 322)
    - Prescription Drug Workgroup 2002 (Box 323)
    - Reimbursement Models (Box 323)
    - 1990-1999, 14 folders (Box 323)
- Faculty Records 1850-1976
  The Faculty Records Subgroup is most notable for an extensive run of Faculty and Executive Faculty minutes (1850-1979). This subgroup also contains records of the annual faculty retreat (1965-1979) where major changes in the Medical School were often discussed at length. There are also minutes of meetings of the Junior Medical Faculty (1956-1968).
  - Faculty and Executive Faculty Minutes
    - 1850-1875, 1 volumes (Box 127)
    - 1878-1891 (Box 128)
      (photocopy; original in Box 178)
    - 1891-1897 (Box 128)
    - 1897-1903 (Box 128)
    - 1905-1910 (Volume 2)
    - 1905-1910 (Volume 2a)
      (continued)
    - 1910-1914 (Volume 3)
    - 1914-1917 (Volume 4)
    - 1917-1923 (Volume 5)
    - 1923-1930 (Volume 6)
    - September 1930-December 1955, 4 volumes (Box 128)
    - January 1956-June 1964, 5 volumes (Box 129)
    - October 1964-January 1969, 6 volumes (Box 130)
    - February 1969-January 1972, 7 volumes (Box 131)
    - February 1972-August 1973, 4 volumes (Box 132)
    - October 1973-December 1976, 6 volumes (Box 133)
  - Miscellaneous Faculty Records
    - Faculty Retreats (Box 134)
      - 1958-1976, 12 folders (Box 134)
    - Junior Medical Faculty Minutes
      - Undated (Box 134)
      - 1956-1968, 11 folders (Box 134)
- Miscellaneous Records
  The subgroup Miscellaneous Records (primarily of the 19th or early 20th century) is an artificially constructed subgroup of miscellaneous documents that have come into the possession of the Bentley Library over the course of a number of years and through a wide variety of sources. All of the documents relate to the Medical School, and many were actually created by the school itself, but were separated from the school's papers. The documents are arranged alphabetically under three categories: Primarily of the 19th or Early 20th Century; Miscellaneous Reports, 1971 and 1979-1982; and School flag / Victor Vaughan Memorial.
  - Primarily of the 19th or Early 20th Century
    - Appropriations Requests 1853-1884 (Box 135)
    - Cheever, Henry S. Report on Work in Therapeutics, Materia Medica and Physiology 1876 (Box 135)
    - Correspondence (Regents Communications) Regarding Admission Requirements and Salaries 1925-1927 (Box 135)
    - Department Reports 1880-1882 (Box 135)
    - Detroit
      - Newspaper Clippings Regarding Relocation of Clinical Work 1889 (Box 135)
      - Proposal to Relocate School 1904-1910, 2 folders (Box 135)
    - Herdman, William, Report on Grave Robbing 1880 (Box 135)
    - Historical File
      - Chronology of Medical Center Development 1840-1969 (Box 135)
      - Encyclopedic Survey Update of Medical Center (Fred Jenner Hodges) 1971 (Box 135)
      - "File of Peckham Committee Papers" (Encyclopedic Update, includes brief departmental histories) 1970-1971 (Box 135)
      - Letter: Alonzo B. Palmer to Joseph Smith, U.S. Army June 28, 1863 (copy) (Box 135)
      - Medical School Seal (Box 135)
    - Homeopathic Hospital Student Petition 1872 (Box 135)
    - Homeopathic Medical School. Letters, pro and con 1895 (Box 135)
    - Huber, G. Carl, Portrait Fund 1931-1932 (Box 135)
    - Institute of Radiological Research Proposal 1945 (Box 135)
    - Medicine and Surgery, Department Development 1850-1915 (oversize) (Box 135)
    - Medical School Annual Reports 1879-1881 (Box 135)
    - Miscellaneous 1894-1903 (Box 135)
    - Pathology, Report on Potential Contributions of Department to War Effort 1917 (Box 135)
    - Physiology, Applications for Professorship in 1878 (Box 135)
    - Recommendations for Appointment of Peter Collier, Robert Kedzie, and Preston Rose 1875 (Box 135)
    - Sewall, Henry
      - Daybook of Physiology Course at Johns Hopkins University 1880 (Box 135)
      - Notes on Practical Physiological Work undated (Box 135)
    - State Board of Medical Examiners Report on the Medical School 1880-1882 (Box 135)
    - State Eclectic Medical Surgical Society 1879 (Box 135)
    - Students
      - Notebook of J.H. Etheridge 1866-1867 (Box 135)
      - Registers of Students
        - 1850-1871 (Box 135)
        - 1851-1866 (Box 135)
        - 1854-1864 (Box 135)
        - 1866-1877 (Box 135)
        - 1877-1891 (Volume 7)
        - ca. 1885 (Volume 8)
      - Register of Alumni circa 1885-1890 (Volume 9)
      - Seating Charts 1885-1886 (Box 135)
    - Vaughan, Victor, Drafts of articles undated (Box 135)
  - Miscellaneous Reports 1971, 1979-1982
    The Reports Series (.75 linear feet) contains miscellaneous reports generated by or about the Medical School. They are arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Clinic Visit Budget 1980-1981 (Box 161)
    - Medical School Curriculum July 1971 (Box 161)
    - Molecular Genetics at the University of Michigan February 1982 (Box 161)
    - Strategic Plan for Medical School, Final Report April 27, 1982 (Box 161)
    - Selected Five and Ten Year Statistics (Box 161)
    - Use of the NBME Part 1 Examination at University of Michigan February 13, 1981 (Box 161)
    - Faculty Conference on Curriculum January 1979, 4 volumes (Box 161)
  - School Flag, Vaughan Memorial
    - Charts Depicting Development of Departments in Medical School, ca. 1945, 1 folders
    - Flag, Medical School 1959
      - Original Design, 1 folders
      - Statement, 1 folders
    - Victor Clarence Vaughan Memorial
      - Resolutions Adopted by the Medical School Faculty 1930 (illuminated), 1 folders
      - Faculty Meeting Minutes January 6, 1930, 1 folders
- Audio-Visual Materials
  - Photographs
    The Medical School Photographs include Faculty portraits, class portraits of students, and photos of medical classes, laboratories, and hospital wards, many of the pre-1900 photos were taken by J. Jefferson Gibson. For the older photos in this series (General Files, Classes by Subject, and Classes by Years through 1925) photocopies are provided for research use. Original photos, located in box 213, are for staff use only. The Gibson photos have been digitized and are available online thought the Bentley Library Image Bank
    - Buildings and Laboratories
      - Buildings (including hospitals) (Box 136)
      - Laboratories, ca. 1890 (from Gibson) (Box 136)
      - Laboratories, ca. 1970s (Box 136)
      - Medical Center (Box 136)
    - Departments (chairmen and section chiefs)
      - Administration
        - Medical School Deans (Box 136)
      - Anatomy (Box 136)
      - Anesthesiology (Box 136)
      - Biochemistry (Box 136)
      - Dermatology (Box 136)
      - Human Genetics (Box 136)
      - Internal Medicine (Box 136)
      - Microbiology (Box 136)
      - Neurology (Box 136)
      - Obstetrics and Gynecology (Box 136)
      - Ophthalmology (Box 136)
      - Otorhinolaryngology (Box 136)
      - Pathology (Box 136)
      - Pediatrics (Box 136)
      - Physical Medicine (Box 136)
      - Physiology (Box 136)
      - Postgraduate Medicine (Box 136)
      - Psychiatry (Box 136)
      - Radiology (Box 136)
      - Surgery (Box 136)
    - General Files
      - Faculty (from album of 1918) (Box 136)
        (photocopies)
      - Faculty-Group photos (Box 136)
        (see also outsize photos)
      - Faculty-Individuals (Box 136)
      - Gibson Photos 1893
        The Gibson Studio of Ann Arbor took a series photos of Medical School classrooms, laboratories, and student and faculty groups in 1983. There are some additional Gibson images which may have been taken at a different time. Access to the high-quality albumen prints is restricted for preservation reasons. Photocopies are available for reference use in the reading room. All of the identifiable Gibson photos have been scanned and are available through the Bentley Library's Image Bank. Links below provide access to the scanned images.
        - Gibson Folder 1 1893, 18 items (Box 136)
          (photocopies). Image IDs: Bl002001-BL002009, BL002011-BL0021019
        - Gibson Folder 2 1893, 17 items (Box 136)
          (photocopies). Image IDs: BL002020-BL002022, BL002025-BLl002037
        - Gibson Folder 3 1893, 22 items (Box 136)
          (photocopies). Image IDs: BL002038-BL002044, BL002046-BL002060
        - Gibson Folder 4 1893, 14 items (Box 136)
          (photocopies). Image IDs: BL002061-BL002066, BL002068-BL002975
      - Life Magazine Photos (Box 136)
      - Medical Center Administration (John Forsyth, Joseph Johnson, George Zuidema, Rhetaugh Dumas), prints (Box 136)
      - Nurses and Nursing (prints) (Box 136)
      - Staff (Box 136)
      - Survival Flight (helicopter) circa 1986, print (Box 136)
      - University Hospital (interiors & exteriors) 1986, undated, prints (Box 136)
    - Classes by Subject
      - Histology Classes, 3 items including 1 Gibson print (Box 136)
      - Surgery and Anatomy Classes
        - Amphitheater Views, Dissections, including 4 Gibson prints; 6 items (Box 136)
        - Groups, formal, including 3 Gibson prints; 5 items (Box 136)
        - Groups, informal, including 3 Gibson prints; 5 items (Box 136)
    - Classes by Years
      - 1872 (Box 136)
      - 1880 (Box 136)
      - 1883 (Box 136)
      - 1885 (Box 136)
      - 1891 (Box 136)
      - 1901 (Box 136)
      - 1918 (Box 136)
      - 1919 (Box 136)
      - 1925 (Box 136)
      - 1952 (Box 136)
      - 1953 (Box 136)
      - 1954 (Box 136)
      - 1955 (Box 136)
      - 1956 (Box 136)
      - 1957 (Box 136)
      - 1958 (Box 136)
      - 1959 (Box 136)
      - 1960 (Box 136)
      - 1961 (Box 136)
      - 1962 (Box 136)
      - 1963 (Box 136)
      - 1964 (Box 136)
      - 1965 (Box 136)
      - 1966 (Box 136)
      - 1967 (Box 136)
      - 1968 (Box 136)
      - 1969 (Box 136)
      - 1970 (Box 136)
      - 1971 (Box 136)
      - 1972 (Box 136)
      - 1973 (Box 136)
      - 1974 (Box 136)
      - 1975 (Box 136)
      - 1976 (Box 136)
      - 1977 (Box 136)
      - 1978 (Box 136)
    - Class Nights (by Years)
      - 1963 or 1964 (Box 136)
      - 1967 (Box 136)
      - 1969 (Box 136)
  - Negatives
    - negatives of class photos (Box 136)
      [Staff use only]
  - Films
    The films series includes 6 reels of 16mm film of University Hospital buildings and construction and one reel on the 1983 Medical Alumni Conference. Additional film and video footage documenting the Medical School or featuring the Medical School faculty can be found in the University of Michigan Media Resources Center and BMC Media Services record groups.
    - University Hospital buildings and construction, 6 film reels 16 mm (Box 136)
      (also of University President Harlan Hatcher)
    - Medical Alumni Conference 89th Annual Open Exercises 1983, 1 film reels 16 mm (Box 136)
  - Outsize Photographs
    (in Bimu/C41 (Faculty) and UBImu/C46 (Classes) medium and large)
    - Faculty (Folder 1)
      (medium and large)
    - Classes by years
      - Unidentified year (Folder 1)
        (group, medium)
      - 1863 (Folder 3)
        (2 in large)
      - 1870-1871 (Folder 1)
        (medium)
      - 1874 (Folder 1)
      - 1879 (Folder 1)
        (medium, large group)
      - 1881 (Folder 1)
      - 1882 (Folder 3)
      - 1883 (Folder 3)
        (large)
      - 1884 (Folder 3)
      - 1885 (Folder 1)
      - 1887 (Folder 3)
      - 1889 (Folder 3)
      - 1890 (Folder 4)
      - 1891 (Folder 4)
      - 1892 (Folder 4)
      - 1893 (Folder 4)
      - 1894 (Folder 4)
        (group, large
      - 1894 (Folder 1)
      - 1895 (Folder 1)
      - 1895 (Folder 4)
        (group, large)
      - 1897 (Folder 4)
      - 1898 (Folder 5)
      - 1899 (Folder 5)
      - 1901 (Folder 5)
      - 1902 (Folder 5)
      - 1903 (Folder 5)
      - 1905 (Folder 5)
      - 1905 (Folder 2)
      - circa 1905 (Folder 2)
        (2 different groups, medium)
      - 1911 (Folder 2)
      - 1912-1913 (Folder 2)
      - 1927 (Folder 5)
      - 1929 (Folder 5)
      - 1929 (Folder 2)
      - 1932 (Folder 5)
    - Gibson Photographs (Folder 6)
  - Drawings
    - Drawing of 1903 Medical Building 1946, 1 folders (Folder 8)
  - Photographs: STAFF USE ONLY (Researchers must use photocopies in Box 136)
    - General Files
      - Faculty (from album of 1918) (Box 213)
      - Faculty-Group Photos (Box 213)
      - Faculty-Individuals (Box 213)
      - Gibson Photographs 1893, 4 folders (Box 213)
      - Gibson Glass Plate Negative (Fragile) (Box 213)
      - Life Magazine Photos (Box 213)
    - Staff (Box 213)
    - Classes by Subject
      - Histology Classes (Box 213)
      - Surgery and Anatomy Classes
        - Amphitheater Views (Box 213)
        - Dissections (Box 213)
        - Groups, formal (Box 213)
        - Groups, informal (Box 213)
    - Classes by Years
      - 1872 (Box 213)
      - 1880 (Box 213)
      - 1883 (Box 213)
      - 1885 (Box 213)
      - 1891 (Box 213)
      - 1901 (Box 213)
      - 1918 (Box 213)
      - 1919 (Box 213)
      - 1925 (Box 213)
- Audio-Visual Materials
  - Photographs (Box 136)
    - Buildings and Laboratories
      - Buildings (including hospitals) (Box 136)
      - Laboratories, ca. 1890 (from Gibson) (Box 136)
      - Laboratories, ca. 1970s (Box 136)
      - Medical Center (Box 136)
    - Departments (chairmen and section chiefs)
      - Administration
        - Medical School Deans (Box 136)
      - Anatomy (Box 136)
      - Anesthesiology (Box 136)
      - Biochemistry (Box 136)
      - Dermatology (Box 136)
      - Human Genetics (Box 136)
      - Internal Medicine (Box 136)
      - Microbiology (Box 136)
      - Neurology (Box 136)
      - Obstetrics and Gynecology (Box 136)
      - Ophthalmology (Box 136)
      - Otorhinolaryngology (Box 136)
      - Pathology (Box 136)
      - Pediatrics (Box 136)
      - Physical Medicine (Box 136)
      - Physiology (Box 136)
      - Postgraduate Medicine (Box 136)
      - Psychiatry (Box 136)
      - Radiology (Box 136)
      - Surgery (Box 136)
    - General Files
      - Faculty (from album of 1918) (Box 136)
      - Faculty-Group photos (Box 136)
      - Faculty-Individuals (Box 136)
      - Gibson Photos 1893 (Box 136)
        - Gibson Folder 1 1893, 18 items (Box 136)
        - Gibson Folder 2 1893, 17 items (Box 136)
        - Gibson Folder 3 1893, 22 items (Box 136)
        - Gibson Folder 4 1893, 14 items (Box 136)
      - Life Magazine Photos (Box 136)